Guide to the Robert Fitzgerald Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1892-1985; Series V; 7.92; (19 boxes)
  - FAMILY PAPERS
    - Fitzgerald, Maria
      - School records, 1964, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 3302)
      - School work, 1959 (Box 94, Folder 3303)
    - Fitzgerald, Michael
      - Bills and receipts, 1966, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 3304)
      - "Boomlay!" script, typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3305)
      - "Chalk," draft, screenplay, typescript, photocopy, 1975 Jun (Box 94, Folder 3306)
        Written with Benedict Fitzgerald
      - Clippings, 1983-84, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3307)
      - "Fitzgerald!" film presentation, typescript, photocopy, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 3308)
      - Printed ephemera, 1953-64, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3309)
      - School records, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 3310)
    - Fitzgerald, Nora M.
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3311)
      - Printed ephemera, 1934 Aug 20 (Box 94, Folder 3312)
    - Fitzgerald, Penelope Laurans
      - Financial records, 1980, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 3313)
      - Introduction to dissertation, draft, typescript, corrected, 1975 Jan (Box 94, Folder 3314)
      - Notebook, [1984?] (Box 94, Folder 3315)
      - Notes in Penelope Laurans Fitzgerald's hand, 1976-78, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3316)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3317)
      - "Robert Lowell, Memorial Hall, Cambridge, 1967" poem, typescript, 1977 Dec (Box 94, Folder 3318)
      - Other papers, 1970-81, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3319)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert Emmet
      - Address book, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3320)
      - Agreement with Nora M. Fitzgerald, 1980 Jun 2 (Box 94, Folder 3321)
      - Application for Admission to Illinois Bar (Box 95, Folder 3322)
      - Bills and receipts, 1904, 1927 (Box 95, Folder 3323)
      - Certificate of marriage, 1905 Sep 12 (Box 95, Folder 3324)
      - Check book and cancelled checks, 1901-26 (Box 95, Folder 3325)
      - Clippings, 1905-61 (Box 95, Folder 3326)
      - Date book, 1903-05 (Box 95, Folder 3327)
      - Empty envelopes, 1909, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3328)
      - Gift card signed by Robert Fitzgerald, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3329)
      - List of clothes, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3330)
      - Medical records, 1907 May 31 (Box 95, Folder 3331)
        Includes letter from Dr. John Ridlon to Dr. Taylor
      - Photographs, [1907?] (Box 95, Folder 3332)
      - Printed ephemera, 1903-14, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3333)
    - Fitzgerald, Robert H.
      - Printed ephemera, 1966 Jun 9 (Box 95, Folder 3334)
    - Fitzgerald, Sarah
      - "Aiken's Search for Self-Awareness," article, printed version, Commonweal, 1952 Nov 14 (Box 95, Folder 3335)
      - Financial records, 1960-79 (Box 95, Folder 3336)
      - Indenture of Trust, 1968 Apr 3 (Box 95, Folder 3337)
      - International Certificate of Vaccination, 1962 Nov 13 (Box 95, Folder 3338)
      - Last Will, 1968 Apr 3 (Box 95, Folder 3339)
      - Notice of Separation from the U.S. Naval Service, 1945 Dec 1 (Box 95, Folder 3340)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3341)
      - Postcards, 1945 Feb (Box 95, Folder 3342)
      - Printed ephemera, 1979 Apr (Box 95, Folder 3343)
      - [Reviews], drafts, typescript carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3344)
      - [Reviews], printed versions, 1952-53 (Box 95, Folder 3345)
      - Soggiorno degli stranieri in Italia, 1953 Dec 9 (Box 95, Folder 3346)
      - Songs of Innocence and Experience by William Blake, printed version, 1938 (Box 95, Folder 3347)
    - Fitzgerald, Ughetta
      - Bills and receipts, 1958-60 (Box 95, Folder 3348)
      - Passport, 1957 Sep 25 (Box 95, Folder 3349)
      - [Poem], draft, typescript, photocopy, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3350)
      - School records, 1964-70, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3351)
    - Green, Eleanor
      - Clippings, 1936 Mar 22 (Box 95, Folder 3352)
      - Fellowship application, 1937 (Box 95, Folder 3353)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3354)
      - [Poems], drafts, typescript and typescript carbon (Box 95, Folder 3355)
    - Linane, Thomas
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3356)
    - Montague, Bernard
      - Letter from Herbert A. Calkins, 1956 Oct 11 (Box 95, Folder 3357)
    - Rahn, Betsy Fitzgerald
      - Clippings, 1964, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 3358)
    - Stuart, Agnes Elizabeth Montague
      - Address book, [1968?] (Box 95, Folder 3359)
      - Bay Pines News, 1957-58 (Box 95, Folder 3360-3362)
      - Clippings and ephemera removed from correspondence, 1935-79, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 3363)
      - Convenant for Perpetual Internment, 1963 Sep 5 (Box 95, Folder 3364)
      - Financial documents, 1943-71 (Box 95, Folder 3365)
      - Last Will and Testament, 1930-47 (Box 96, Folder 3366)
      - "A Little Belgian Boy's New Year's Day," draft, story, typescript carbon, corrected, [ca. 1917] (Box 96, Folder 3367)
      - Material relating to the estate of Agnes Stuart, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 3368)
      - Medical records, 1948, 1951 (Box 96, Folder 3369)
      - Military records, 1919 (Box 96, Folder 3370)
      - Miscellaneous notes, [1936-46?], n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3371)
      - Notebook on Agnes Stuart in hand of Robert Fitzgerald, 1965-66 (Box 96, Folder 3372)
      - Photographs, 1951-66, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3373)
      - [Poems], drafts, holograph, 1946, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3374)
        Includes copy of poem by Catherine Cunnigham
      - Printed ephemera, 1943-71, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3375)
      - Receipt for Insured Mail, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3376)
      - School notebook, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3377)
      - Tourist pass, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 3378)
      - "A Tribute," draft, tribute, holograph, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3379)
    - Stuart, Anne
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3380)
    - Stuart, Daniel Delehanty Vincent
      - Biographical statement, 1948-49 (Box 96, Folder 3381)
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3382)
    - Stuart, [Gerald?]
      - Photograph, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3383)
    - Stuart, John McHugh Jr. ("Jack")
      - Clippings, 1966 May 22
      - The Port Weekly, 1932-33 (Box 96, Folder 3384)
      - "Wings Over America: The Future of Air Poweer," article, printed version, 1946 Feb (Box 96, Folder 3385)
    - Stuart, John McHugh
      - Obituary, 1957 Dec 25 (Box 96, Folder 3386)
    - [Stuart, William A.?]
      - Photograph, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3387)
    - Other
      - Business cards, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3388)
      - Genealogical information, 1979, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3389)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3390-3391)
  - MATERIAL RELATING TO TIME MAGAZINE
    - [Address] at Celebration Dinner, 1943 Mar 11 (Box 96, Folder 3392)
    - Annual Report to Stockholders, 1939-42 (Box 96, Folder 3393)
    - "Author's Roundup", 1947 Jun (Box 96, Folder 3394)
    - Printed ephemera, 1937-48 (Box 96, Folder 3395)
    - Prospectus, 1938-1943 (Box 96, Folder 3396)
    - Other material, 1946, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3397)
  - MEDICAL RECORDS
    - Correspondence, 1932-48, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3398)
      Includes third-party letter
    - Exam results and reports, 1942-84 (Box 96, Folder 3399)
    - International Certificate of Inoculation and Vaccination, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 3400)
    - Prescriptions, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 3401)
    - Other documents, 1978 Feb (Box 96, Folder 3402)
  - MILITARY RECORDS
    - Alphabetical lists of 5th Batallion, 1943 Jun 28 (Box 97, Folder 3403)
    - Annual Qualifications Questionnaire, 1951-52 (Box 97, Folder 3404)
    - Appointment to U.S. Naval Reserves, 1943 May 15 (Box 97, Folder 3405)
    - Authorization for Conducted Sight Seeing Tour, 1945 Jul 6 (Box 97, Folder 3406)
    - Certificates, 1945-46 (Box 97, Folder 3407)
    - CINCPAC and CINCPOA Staff Directory, 1945 Aug 1 (Box 97, Folder 3408)
    - Foreign Intelligence Correspondence Course Assignments (Box 97, Folder 3409)
    - Memos and communications, 1943-45, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3410-3411)
    - Naval Communications Assignments, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3412)
    - Navigation H Work, n.d.
    - Notebook, [ca. 1943-45] (Box 97, Folder 3413)
    - Notice of Separation from the U.S. Naval Service, 1945 Dec 26 (Box 97, Folder 3414)
    - Officer's Qualification Record, 1944-45 (Box 97, Folder 3415)
    - Photographs, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3416)
      Includes photograph by U.S. Navy
    - Printed ephemera, 1945, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3417)
    - Report of Physical Examination, 1943 Jun 16 (Box 97, Folder 3418)
    - U. S. Naval Training School, Armed Guard Gunnery material, 1944 Jun 17 (Box 97, Folder 3419)
    - Other material, 1942-45, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3420)
  - NOTES AND NOTEBOOKS
    - "Aeneid III IV V VI VII", 1949-50 (Box 97, Folder 3420a)
    - "Douglas [Surrey?] Stanley...", n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3421)
    - "French", 1946 (Box 97, Folder 3422)
    - "Inferno & Purgatorio, 1st notes", n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3423)
    - "Italian", n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3424)
    - "Italian II", n.d. (Box 97, Folder 3425)
    - "Italian Verse", n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3426)
    - [On Homer's Odyssey ], n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3427)
    - [On Italian], n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3428)
    - "Oxford Book of American Verse", [1962 Jul?] (Box 98, Folder 3429)
    - "Paradiso", n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3430)
    - "Paradiso", n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3431)
    - "Sophocles... Virgil Aen I & II", n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3432)
    - "Spanish 1940-41-42", 1940-42 (Box 98, Folder 3433)
    - "Things to Remember", 1929 (Box 98, Folder 3434)
    - "La Vita Nuova", n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3435)
    - "Vita Nuova & Inferno", n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3436)
    - Untitled, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3437)
    - Untitled, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3438)
    - Untitled, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3439)
    - Untitled, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 3440)
    - Untitled, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3441)
    - Untitled, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3442)
    - Untitled, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3443)
    - Untitled, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3444)
    - [Loose notes], 1953-78, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3445-3451)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Photographs of Robert Fitzgerald
      - Fitzgerald, Robert, 1915-84, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3452)
        With Martha Berryman and unidentified others
        Includes photographs by Paul Koby and Henri Cole
    - Photographs of Others
      - Berryman, John, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3453)
        With unidentified children
      - Carrier, Katherine, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3454)
      - Drummond, Andrea (Box 99, Folder 3455)
        With [Patricia Barbora?]
      - Elliot, Malcolm, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3456)
      - [Fitts?], Dudley, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3457)
        With "Deborah," "Danny," Maria Ivancic, and children
      - Hartle, John, 1952 (Box 99, Folder 3458)
      - Massola, Giuseppe, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3459)
      - Morgan family children, 1959 May (Box 99, Folder 3460)
      - Morris family children, 1959 Nov (Box 99, Folder 3461)
      - Nims family children, 1959, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 3462)
      - [Thompson?], ----, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 3463)
      - First name only, 1949-61, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3464)
      - Unidentified, 1949-65, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3465-3466)
    - Other photographs
      - Artwork, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3467)
        Includes photographs by Walter Engel
      - Kennebec River, 1984 Nov (Box 99, Folder 3468)
      - Religious event and icon, 1954, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 3469)
      - Theaterical presentation at Mt. Holyoke, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 3470)
        Includes photographs of RF
        Photographs by Vincent S. D'Addario
      - Unidentified places, 1949-64, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 3471)
  - PRINTED EPHEMERA
    - Announcements
      - Appearances by Robert Fitzgerald, 1954-84, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 3472-3473)
      - Other events, 1934-84, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 3474-3477)
    - Brochures, pamphlets, and promotional material
      - Academy of American Poets, 1953-83, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 3478-3479)
      - British Museum, 1961-68, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 3480)
      - New Hall, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 3481)
      - Others, 1933-84 (Box 100, Folder 3482-3487)
      - Others, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3488-3491)
    - Businss Cards
      - Fitzgerald, Robert, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3492)
      - Delaney, J. A., 1915-23, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3493)
      - Others, 1969-78, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3494)
    - Invitations
      - Academy of American Poets, 1971-84 (Box 101, Folder 3495)
      - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1970-81 (Box 101, Folder 3496)
      - Gotham Book Mart, 1977-82 (Box 101, Folder 3497)
      - Harvard University, 1977-84, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3498)
      - Other events, 1945-84, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3499-3504)
    - Periodicals
      - Aileron, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 3505)
      - Bulletin -- American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1976, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 3506)
      - The Campus, 1952-53
      - Cinc Packet, 1945 (Box 102, Folder 3507)
      - The Daily Princetonian, 1951-52
      - Grand Street, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 3508)
      - Harvard Alumni Bulletin, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 3509)
      - Harvard Bulletin, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 3510)
      - The Harvard Crimson, 1974 Jun 12
      - Harvard University. Dept. of Comparative Literature Newsletter, 1970-83 (Box 102, Folder 3511)
      - High Time, 1939 (Box 102, Folder 3512)
      - Hokah Chief, 1952
      - MPA Newsletter, 1979-82 (Box 102, Folder 3513)
      - The Monstrance, 1957 (Box 102, Folder 3514)
      - MSS, 1950-51 (Box 102, Folder 3515)
      - The New Republic, 1953 Mar 30 (Box 102, Folder 3516)
      - The New Yorker, 1933, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 3517-3518)
      - Parent's Choice, 1981
      - PEN American Center Newsletter, 1977, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 3519)
      - Poetry Pilot, 1976-84 (Box 102, Folder 3520)
      - Radcliffe Quarterly, 1972 Mar (Box 102, Folder 3521)
      - The Tablet, 1950 Sep 2 (Box 102, Folder 3522)
      - Time, 1972 Mar 6 (Box 102, Folder 3523)
      - Others, 1944-83, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 3524-3526)
    - Programs for memorial services, concerts, conferences, theatrical, and other events
      - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1971-83 (Box 103, Folder 3527-3528)
      - Phi Beta Kappa. Massachusetts Alpha (Harvard University), 1977-83 (Box 103, Folder 3529)
      - Others, 1921-85, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 3530-3536)
    - Other material
      - American Friends of Cambridge University, 1974, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 3537)
      - Blank cards, 1959, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 3538)
      - Blank stationary, 1963, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 3539)
      - Culver Summer Schools, 1926, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 3540)
      - Driver's manual, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 3541)
      - Exhibition catalogs and publicity, 1953-84, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3542)
      - Gift certificates, 1977 Oct 12 (Box 104, Folder 3543)
      - Golf cards, 1978-81, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3544)
      - Identification and membership cards, 1934-81 (Box 104, Folder 3545)
      - Key to the "Standard" Edition of Italian Grammar (Box 104, Folder 3546)
      - Maps, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3547)
      - Material relating to American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1977, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3548)
      - Material relating to American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1978-85, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3549)
      - Material relating to Harvard University, 1970-83, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3550-3552)
      - Material relating to honorary degree from Yale, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 3553)
      - Menus, 1976-78, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3554)
      - Postcards, 1960, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3555)
      - Religious ephemera, 1946-80, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3556)
      - Sweepstake receipts, 1932-33 (Box 104, Folder 3557)
      - Thankyou cards, 1975-82, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3558)
      - Tickets and ticket stubs, 1977-78, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3559)
      - Works celebrating Handel's Acis and Galatea, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 3560)
      - Other material, 1947-84, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3561)
  - REAL ESTATE
    - 14 Fernald Drive, Apt. 32, Cambridge, Mass., 1978-81 (Box 104, Folder 3562)
    - 20 Bryant Street, Cambridge, Mass., 1966-72, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3563)
    - 70 Acres Road, Redding, Conn., n.d.
    - 6812 48 Ave. No., n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3564)
    - Villa Camogli, 1955-56 (Box 104, Folder 3565)
    - Villa Fiesole, 1959 Nov (Box 104, Folder 3566)
    - Villa La Mandrella, 1953-56, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3567)
    - Villa ("Le Lagore") Levanto, 1958-59 (Box 104, Folder 3568)
    - Villa San Fortunato della Collina, Perugia, 1961-79, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3569)
      See also: Correspondence, Sforzolini, Luigi-Giacomo Scassellati, Box 34, folder 1286
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3570)
  - SCHOOL RECORDS
    - Saint Agnes Catholic School
      - Monthly, Term and Annual Report, 1921-24 (Box 105, Folder 3571)
      - Receipts, 1922-24 (Box 105, Folder 3572)
    - Springfield High School
      - Instructor's Report, 1924-25, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 3573)
      - Photocopies of yearbook pages, 1928 (Box 105, Folder 3574)
    - The Choate School
      - Invoice, 1928 Oct 1 (Box 105, Folder 3575)
      - Photocopies of reports, 1929, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 3576)
      - Photocopy of commencement speech, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 3577)
      - Prize Day program, 1929 May 25 (Box 105, Folder 3578)
    - Harvard University
      - Bluebook, n.y. Jan 5 (Box 105, Folder 3579)
      - Certificate of Admission, 1929 Jul 16 (Box 105, Folder 3580)
      - Collateral report, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 3581)
      - Commencement program, [1933 Jun 22?] (Box 105, Folder 3582)
      - Grade reports, 1930 Jun 30 (Box 105, Folder 3583)
      - Press release, 1933 Jun 22 (Box 105, Folder 3584)
        Includes text of Latin oration by Fitzgerald
      - Printed ephemera, 1930, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 3585)
    - Cambridge University
      - Addresses, [ca. 1931-32] (Box 105, Folder 3586)
      - Financial records, 1932 (Box 105, Folder 3587)
      - Printed ephemera, 1928-31, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 3588)
  - SPEAKING ENGAGEMENTS
    - British Speaking Tour
      - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 3589-3590)
        Includes notes from C[ecil?] Day Lewis, Bonamy Dobrée, Douglas Grant, David Daiches, Laurence Whistler, Marcus Cunliffe, Peter Levi, and others
      - Copies of poems, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 3591)
      - Guest List for Reception, 1962 Oct 9 (Box 105, Folder 3592)
      - Invitation, [1962 Oct 12] (Box 105, Folder 3593)
      - Itineraries, 1962 Oct (Box 105, Folder 3594)
      - Notes, [1962 Oct 9?] (Box 105, Folder 3595)
      - Publicity, 1962 Oct (Box 105, Folder 3596)
      - Receipts, 1962 Oct (Box 105, Folder 3597)
  - TEACHING AND COURSE MATERIAL
    - Harvard University
      - Book Information Form, 1969-81 (Box 105, Folder 3598)
      - Boylston Prize, 1969-77, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 3599)
      - Comments on student theses, 1976-79 (Box 105, Folder 3600)
      - Comparative Literature 201 course material, 1964-80, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 3601-3605)
      - Comparative Literature Department material, 1973-84 (Box 105, Folder 3606)
      - Course lists, 1966-81 (Box 105, Folder 3607)
      - Dunster House material, 1970-77 (Box 105, Folder 3608)
      - English 103-s-d course material, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3609)
      - English 283 course material, 1965-76, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3610)
      - English Car course material, 1973-79, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3611)
      - English Cbr course material, 1977, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3612)
      - English Department material, 1970-83, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3613)
      - English T[ar] course material, 1966-81, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3614)
      - Harvard Cooperative Society Textbook Dept., 1973-79 (Box 106, Folder 3615)
      - Grade sheets, 1981 Mar 25 (Box 106, Folder 3616)
      - List of PhD Candidates, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 3617)
      - Material relating to Gwendolyn Brooks' reading, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 3618)
        Includes photograph of Brooks
      - Minutes and agendas, 1972-80 (Box 106, Folder 3619)
      - Other course material, 1964-79, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3620-3622)
      - President's Report, 1951-52 (Box 106, Folder 3623)
      - Resumés and CVs, 1964-79, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3624)
      - School calendars and schedules, 1964-81 (Box 106, Folder 3625)
      - Student applications and letters, 1968-79, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 3626-3627)
      - Student bluebooks, 1965-79, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 3628-3629)
      - Student translations, 1977, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 3630)
      - Student writing, 1970-79, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 3631-3632)
      - Other documents, 1970-84, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 3633-3634)
    - Indiana University School of Letters
      - Admission cards, 1951, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 3635)
      - Loose notes, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 3636-3639)
      - Student lists, 1951, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 3640)
      - Virgil and the Virgilian Tradition course material, 1952 (Box 107, Folder 3641)
    - Mount Holyoke College
      - English 335 course material, 1963-64 (Box 108, Folder 3642)
    - Notre Dame
      - Summary of Notes & Questions, 1957 May (Box 108, Folder 3643)
    - Princeton University
      - Bouts Rimés, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 3644)
      - Directory, 1950-51 (Box 108, Folder 3645)
      - List of "Princeton Seminar Figures", n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3646)
      - Memorandum on the Development of the Humanities at Princeton University, 1952 Dec 3 (Box 108, Folder 3647)
      - Seminar notes and drafts (Box 108, Folder 3648)
      - Student letters, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3649)
      - Student writing, 1949-50, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3650)
        Includes work by William Jerry Boney anf others
      - Telephone directory, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 3651)
      - Other documents, 1950-51, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3652)
    - Sarah Lawrence College
      - Clippings, 1950, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3653)
        Includes printed and draft correspondence between Fitzgerald and Harold Taylor in The Campus
      - College and faculty documents, 1950-52, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3654)
      - Commencement program, 1950 May 24 (Box 108, Folder 3655)
      - "A Note from Princeton", n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3656)
      - Other course material and notes, 1947-49, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3657)
      - Poetry and prosody course material, 1953, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3658)
      - Student letters, 1947, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3659)
      - [Student writing?], 1947-52, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3660)
      - Thought and Image course material, 1948, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3661)
      - Virgil and Dante course assignments, 1951 (Box 108, Folder 3662)
    - University of Florida
      - Notice of Appointment, 1975 Mar 4 (Box 108, Folder 3663)
    - Unidentified
      - Lecture notes, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3664-3666)
      - Other material, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3667)
  - OTHER MATERIAL
    - Biographical material on Robert Fitzgerald, 1957-82, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3668)
    - Biographical material on others, 1970-76, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3669)
    - Certification of Birth (photocopy), 1910 Oct 12 (Box 108, Folder 3670)
    - "Catholic Matters", 1951-52, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3671)
    - Copies of lyrics to songs by Françoise Hardy, 1974-76, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3672)
    - Directions, 1963-78, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 3673)
    - Dried flowers, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 3674)
    - Empty frame, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 3675)
    - Equation Analysis Test, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 3676)
    - Excerpts, 1969-79, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 3676a)
    - Fellowship applications, 1937-73, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 3677)
    - [Fellowship candidates?] (Box 109, Folder 3678)
    - Harvard Class of 1993 reunion, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 3679)
    - Invitations, 1970-73 (Box 109, Folder 3680)
    - Itineraries, 1963-79, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 3681)
    - Key and envelope, 1935 (Box 109, Folder 3682)
    - Library call slips, 1962 Oct (Box 109, Folder 3683)
    - Lists of books and belongings, 1940, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 3684)
    - Lists of corrections to unidentified writings, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 3685)